



Address : Gamla Huddingevägen 486 / Älvsjö - Stockholm

Phone : 0769637390

Email : bdrgcmz@gmail.com

Linkedin : https://www.linkedin.com/in/bedirgocmez/

Github : https://github.com/bedirgcmz

Profile Site : <u>bedirgocmez.com</u>

SUMMARY & OBJECTIVES

My goal is to adapt to Sweden as quickly as possible and become a tax-paying Swedish citizen. I work hard for this and continue to learn both Swedish culture and Swedish. Now I want to use the work experience I have gained in teaching for many years in the field of IT. I hope to contribute to the Swedish society with the IT trainings I have received.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

- ✓ Currently, I continue to work as a Frontend Developer on my own projects.
- ✓ During the academic year 2018-2020, I worked as a student coach at Happy Education Educational institute.
- ✓ During the academic year 2014-2016, I worked as a primary school teacher at Toros Skola.
- ✓ During the academic year 2011-2014, I worked as a primary school teacher at Rainbow School.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer (08/2021 - 07/2022) I had a nice educational process that lasted 11 months. I learned a lot from this training.

Modern Web Programming (10/2020 - 04/2021) I took 110 hours of HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and React lessons on the Udemy course application.

Student Coaching (10/2018 - 12/2018 **)** Online education, tracking distance courses, online exams and international certificates.

Primary School Graduate Education (09/2014 - 07/2016 **)** I received 2 years of postgraduate training. I completed my thesis on "The effect of the debate technique in the primary school fourth grade social science course on course success and critical thinking".

Primary School Teaching Undergraduate (09/2007 - 06/2011 **)** I have successfully completed my 4-year undergraduate degree.

COMPUTER SKILLS

I really love the computer. I have my own computer since 2008. I do all my work myself. I can use all windows office programs effectively. I also used many different programs at the amateur level (photoshop, coreldraw etc.). With the IT course I took in 2021, I further improved my computer skills.

Software languages I know::

1- Html	5- React	10- Github
2- Css	6- MySql	11- Agile
3- Bootstrap	7- NodeJs	12- Jira
4- Javascript	8- Git	13- Figma

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- English B1
- Swedish SFI-D
- Turkish Very Good (Like mother tongue)
- Kurdish Mother tongue

INTERESTS

My interests are Watching movies, music, travel, sports, and writing a poem.

PERSONAL CHARACTERISTICS

- ✓ As a person, I like to work regularly, carefully, in a group and independently.
- ✓ I find it easy to communicate with people and I like to take personal responsibility. I am also helpful and considerate of other people, yet goal-oriented and cooperative.
- ✓ I like to try new teaching methods.
- ✓ I learn quickly.
- ✓ I am responsible.
- ✓ I like to compromise.

ORGANIZATIONAL SKILLS

When I was in university I had students that I coached. I did many activities with them. I organized trips. While I was a teacher and coach, I led many organizations. I worked as an assistant principal at a private educational institution. I worked in voluntary associations. I participated in many activities.